{"questions":[{"question":"what is Agile?","answers":["treats analysis, design, coding, and testing as discrete phases the project","iterative approach software delivery that builds software incrementally","a name of an angel","kind of development plan"],"correct_ans":"2","level":"1","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"What is right about Agile?","answers":["Requirements can change and be implemented quickly","Working software is the primary measure of success","All the answers are correct","No answer is correct"],"correct_ans":"3","level":"2","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"What is the main goal of a SRR?","answers":["draft documents for the project","documentation Planning and designing the user interface (GUI)","has detailed development plan of the system: methods,models ,etc ","to ensure that the system requirements, products and milestones are defined"],"correct_ans":"4","level":"2","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"What are partial requirements?","answers":["a requirement that is implied in two ways","a requirement that is partially good","incomplete requirement,that doesn\u0027t cover the required functionality in a case","a requirement is missing and is not described at all in the document"],"correct_ans":"3","level":"3","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"walkthrough peer-review is?","answers":["a formal, scheduled activity where a designer presents a design to his team","feedback conversation with the team manager","activity where a designer presents someone else\u0027s design to the team","routine conversation with team members"],"correct_ans":"1","level":"3","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"What is surveyed in a proposal survey?","answers":["ability to meet commitment(the organization and the customer )","all the answers are correct","customer requirements are clarified and properly documented","costs: price, resources, time"],"correct_ans":"2","level":"3","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"What is the Observer pattern?","answers":["None of the answer are correct ","pattern that lets an object ask to be notified when another object changes","this pattern is implemented as an abstract class","pattern that creates an object and isolates a client from which class he created"],"correct_ans":"2","level":"1","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"What is Client-Server architecture?","answers":["more then one answer is correct","collection of services that I can get from a server or a variety servers","the client always starts communicating with the server","the behavior of the system will be in the give and take method "],"correct_ans":"2","level":"3","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"What are Lehman laws?","answers":["refer to study of changes that software systems go through during their lives","contract on system maintenance terms","user interface design rules","legal precedent showing how important maintenance is "],"correct_ans":"1","level":"1","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"What is wrong to say about software maintenance costs?","answers":["usually development costs are greater than maintenance costs","Maintenance costs more than hardware ","maintenance costs are usually higher than development costs","the older the software, the more it costs to develop"],"correct_ans":"1","level":"2","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"What is driver?","answers":["a component that makes a simple simulation of the world around it","component that replaces the UNIT environment and activates test component ","the component on which we want to perform the test","a component that transmits test results"],"correct_ans":"2","level":"2","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"What is the difference between a \u0027white box\u0027 and a \u0027black box\u0027 test?","answers":["there is no difference","various staff members perform the tests","white box refer component in the system but not his code compared to black ","black box refer component in the system but not his code compared to white"],"correct_ans":"4","level":"1","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"What is SDP?","answers":["has detailed development plan of the system: methods,models ,etc ","to ensure that the system requirements, products and milestones are defined","documentation Planning and designing the user interface (GUI)","none of the above"],"correct_ans":"1","level":"2","team":"Scorpions"},{"question":"What on the list is a type of survey?","answers":["product approval","product release review ","per reviews","all of the answers are correct"],"correct_ans":"4","level":"2","team":"Scorpions"}]}